(Amy:)because Google changed
their font?
(Meemaw:)Young lady,
(Meemaw:)if you think I don't know
(Meemaw:)what it's like to live
(Meemaw:)with a stubborn,
egotistical man,
(Meemaw:)then you're wrong.
'Cause that was my husband.
(Leonard:)Really?
(sighs)
(Meemaw:)There were days I wanted to fill
his pockets with corn
(Meemaw:)and toss him in the pigpen.
(Amy:)Well, if you understand,
(Amy:)then why are you giving me
such a hard time?
(Meemaw:)Because when you broke up
with Sheldon,
(Meemaw:)it hurt him deeply,
(Meemaw:)and I don't want to see
that happen again.
(door opens)
(Penny:)Hi. Sorry.
(Penny:)Sheldon would like
to say something to you.
SHELDON:
No, I wouldn't.
(Leonard:)Just get in here.
(Sheldon:)Hello.
(Penny:)Go ahead.
(Sheldon:)Meemaw, look,
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry, but...
(Sheldon:)I have to defend
(Sheldon:)my girlfriend to you.
(Amy:)Oh, Sheldon, thank you.
(Sheldon:)Oh, great, now you're gonna
get emotional.